{
    "subject": "resource/Percy_the_Small_Engine",
    "predicate": "ontology/voice",
    "object": "resource/Martin_Sherman_(actor)",
    "human_readable": "The voice of Percy the Small Engine is Martin Sherman (actor).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9040741324424744,
            "question": "Who voices Percy the Small Engine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9028634428977966,
            "question": "What is the name of the engine that Martin Sherman voices?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8376116156578064,
            "question": "Name a character voiced by Martin Sherman."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8360783457756042,
            "question": "What character does Martin Sherman voice?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8248110413551331,
            "question": "Is Martin Sherman an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8070660829544067,
            "question": "Does Martin Sherman voice any other characters besides Percy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7437548041343689,
            "question": "Who is the voice actor behind Percy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7228338718414307,
            "question": "In what type of media does Martin Sherman's voice acting appear?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.591230034828186,
            "question": "What is Martin Sherman known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.376665860414505,
            "question": "What is the genre of the media featuring Percy the Small Engine?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The voice of Percy the Small Engine is Martin Sherman (actor).",
            "html": "dbpedia_4410_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Martin Sherman known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4410_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what type of media does Martin Sherman's voice acting appear?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4410_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is the voice actor behind Percy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4410_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4410_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4410_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4410_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4410_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4410_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4410_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4410_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4410_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4410_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4410_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. Martin T. Sherman provides voices for Thomas, Percy, and Diesel in the U.S. version of the show, dubbed Thomas and Friends. He also quits voicing these characters due to not being paid enough, and it is mentioned that he voices Percy."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information that supports this statement. Specifically, multiple entries mention Martin T. Sherman's role as the voice actor for Percy and Thomas in the show \"Thomas and Friends.\" For instance:\n\n- From `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4410/re-ranker-msmarco/89.txt`, it states, \"Martin T. Sherman, who voices the train engines Thomas, Percy and Diesel in the U.S. version of the show, dubbed Thomas and Friends.\"\n- From `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4410/re-ranker-msmarco/2.txt`, it mentions, \"But now Sherman, who also voices Thomas' sidekick Percy and the villainous Diesel, has quit after contract negotiations with the show's production company, Hit Entertainment, broke down.\"\n\nThese details confirm that Martin T. Sherman indeed provided the voice for Percy the Small Engine."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}